Finding Aid for the Norman Cousins Papers LSC.1385
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Volume 1
  - Document Case # 79. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 7. Folder. C - 2 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Mrs. Bennet Cerf, Stanley Chapman, Leo Cherne, Lynn Williams., Montrose Newman-Childrens Press, Sidonie Gruenberg-Child Study Assoc. of Am., W. Dix-Chinese Embassy, Katy Christopherson, Russell Church, S. A. Anthony-Civilian Protection Group, Joseph Clark, Urana Clarke, Helen Clarkson, Reverend Claxton, General Lusius Clay, Wilson Clough, Bob Cluett, Vesder Colangelo, Disney MoKeen-Colby College, George Cole, Howard Collins, E. A. Borgese-Committee to Frame a World Constitution, Thomas Collinoon, Philip Culuschuas, Richard Clurman, Charles St. Thomas-Columbia Univ., Collier's All-Scholastic, Everett Clinchy, R. P. Compton, Conscription News, Elihu Stamm-Cooper, Richard Cordell, Norman Cornish, Louis Cowan, Thomas Coward, Fleur Cowles, Neal Cross, Allan Cranston, Larabie Cunningham, Ernest Simmons-Curcent Digest of the Soviet Press, The Real Danger - Fear of Ideas by Henry Steele Commager.
  - Document Case # 80. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. D. (Box 320)
      R. Buvall, Richard Walsh-John Day Co., Jonathan Daniels, Elmer Davis, Charles Dollard, A. Den Doolaard, Beatride Desfosses, J. G. Dickey, Norman Draper, Whitney Darrow, Senator Douglas, Louis Thomas Virginuis Dabney, Henry Dana, Leigh Banenberg, Bill Dauforth, Margery Darrell, Carlos Davila, Hassoldt Davis, Martha Davis, Vera Micheles Dean, Mary Gould Davis, Brooks Emeny, Victoria B. Demarest, Aleda Barclay Sec't to Judge Wm Denman, Edison Dick, Marion Dodd, Fairfax Downey, Emanael Demby, Charles Denhard, Lee Barker-Double-day and Eo., Prof. John Downs, Donald Dunham, Theodore Waller
    - 2. Folder. Encyclopedia Britannica, articles, John V. Dodge, Walter Yust-Ed. (Box 320)
    - 3. Folder. Freedom House. George Field, minutes, Authority in an Unbelieving Worldby Leo Cherne (Box 320)
    - 4. Folder. Fast, Howard. articles, newspaper clippings. (Box 320)
    - 5. Folder. G. (Box 320)
      Johanna Grant, Peter Grimm, Antoni Gronowicz, Norman Richardson-Gettysburg College, Joseph Grew, Lewis Gannett, Hudson Grunewald, Harry Green, John Gleason, Alan Green, Bishop Gilbert of N.Y., Tom Groessemer, CR. Graham, Den Raeburn-Gaer Assoc., C G Gaum, Larry Gara, Edith Garthe, Kenneth Gebbie, Robert Hutchins, Samuel Goldwyn, Mrs. W.J. Goodwin, Cord Meyer Jr., John Temple Graves, Walter Gray, Elinor Green, Wm Grouse, Thomas Wilson, Sidney Satenstein, Diggory Venn, John Gunther
    - 6. Folder. Hackett. correspondence, article, pamphlets (an American School, The Riverdale Plan for Peace Through School Experience.) (Box 320)
    - 7. Folder. Hillver Piece, Bollinger - Pantheon. (Box 320)
      Luther Evans, Robert Gooch, Hon. James Patterson, Archie MacLeish, Jacob Javits, articles, Ezra Loomis Pound, John Davis Lodge, Mary Ella Hopkins, Alexander Lindey, Harrison Smith, John Lewis, Kurt Wolff
    - 8. Folder. Holiday-Standard Oil. corres. (Box 320)
    - 9. Folder. H - 1 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Hornell Hart, John Haynes Holmes, CC Hamenway, Wilna Hervey, Bernice E. Hicks, Gladys Huss, Robert Hutchins, Dale Warren-Houghton Mifflin, John Hohenberg, Frank Hacket, Ben Hall, Oscar Hammerstein, Edward Harris, Doris Flowers-Henry Holt and Co., Alexander Hehmeyer, Carle Hodge, Mortimer Hays, John Hersey, Frank Hackett, Stanley Heath, Alan Hathway, Raymond Hurel, Wm Hitzig, James Humphry III, Alfred Lilienthal-HELP, Hornell Hart, Laura Hobson, Hans Hackenbruch, Alan Haemer, Hiran Haydn, Les Hafner, David Hall, Gordon Halstead, Mrs. Morgan Hamilton, Russell Hamilton, Jane Hammer, Herbert Harris, Henry Hanson, Herdis Hanson.
  - Document Case # 81. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. H - 2 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Herdis Hanson, Henry Hanson, Howard Hanson, Russell Lynes-Harper's Magazine, Victor Hass, Robert Betts-Harcourt, Brace & Co., Hadassah Winer-Harper & Bros., Robert H. Haynes-Harvard College Library, Arthur Garfield Hays, Francis Hayes, H. Nugent Head, Paul Brooks-Houghton Mifflin, Quincy Howe, Garland Evans Hopkins, Chat Paterson-Committee for the Nation's Health, James Hearst, Stanley High, Lilian Britt Heinsohn, Henry Sloane Coffin-Holyland Emergency Liaison Program, Hugo Saclio-Hillyer College, Joseph Hirsh, William Hitzig, Laura Hobson, Thayer Hobson, Rita J. Crocker-Hockaday School, John Haynes Holmes, Paul Hoffman, Hollenbeck, Norman Hood, Sidney Hooz., P. McManus-Houghton Mifflin, Martha Huddleston, Katherine Hruska, Ben Huebsch, R. Bruce Hughes, Robert Hutchins, Harold Hurwitz, Laurence Hyde.
    - 2. Folder. I. (Box 320)
      Frances Grant-International League for the Rights of Man, Samuel Guy InmanFather Albert Murray-Information, John Ivey, Mr. Intner, Harold Ickes, Charles Ikle, Genevieve Schneider-Intercollegian, Ilma's Grapevine, Richard Byrd-Iron Curtain Refugee Campaign.
    - 3. Folder. Integrated Education--Foundation. (Box 320)
      correspondence, articles, newsletter, Fritz Kunz-Counsellor on Studies, Emmet Lavery, Gordon Halstead, Draft for the foundation, Agenda and Supplementary Material for Organizational Meeting of the Research Coordinating Board, The World Institute-A Proposal for a Scientific Institute Devoted to Integrated Cultural, Ethical, and Economic World Progress by Julius Stulman, The Recovery of Culture, Doris Hoffman, Issuxes in Integration.
    - 4. Folder. J. (Box 320)
      Robert Jungle, Marvin Fisher Jones, Rebecca Jarard, Stanley Jones, Albin Johnson, Wallace Harrison, Jan Juta, Malcolm Jones, Ben Javits, JL Teller-Office of Jewish Information, Robert Johnson, Helen Fried Joseph
    - 5. Folder. K. (Box 320)
      Philip Kurland, K, Karvano, Albert Ralph Korn, Sholdon Karlan, Grayson King, Howard Kurtz, Father James Keller-The Christophers, Hans Kaltenborn, Kiyoshi, John Boynton Kaiser, Horace Kallen, Rolf Kalterborn, Alberta Kelley, CO Wright-Kansas State Teachers Assoc., J.M. Kaplan, Janet Rodgers Kaye, Roger Keane, Frances Keene, Jim Kelly, Joseph Joel Keith, Chester Kerr, Marion Kenworthy, Harry Kern, Wm Heard Kilpatrick, Andrew Kind, Elizabeth Kingsley, Clark Kinnaird, Alfred Knopf, Wm Cole-Alfred Knopf, Inc., Sidney Kingsley, Ed Kuhn, Leon Kochuitzky, Fritz Kunz, Howard Kuttz
    - 6. Folder. L -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Peter Lavan, Emmet Lavery, Max Lerner, Amy Freeman Lee, Philip Lesserman III, Erich Leinsdorf, Herbert Lehman, Mrs. Robert Dehman, Sonia Levisnthal, SM Levitas, Adele Levy, Nathan Levin, Donald Romm Levy, Mrs. David M. Levy, Ralph Leyden, Henry Link, David Lilienthal, Edward Litchfield, John Davis Lodge, Robert Low, Merrylen Townsend Lerman, Marguerite Livingston, Wm. Bross Lloyd, Roger Loomis, Marion Canby, Savoie Lottinville, Margaret Floyd, Storer Lunt, Louis Lusky, Isaac Don Levine, Edward Litchfield, J.K. Lasser, Frederick Lewis, Leo Lania, Jessica Lewis, William Lawrence, Christopher LaFarge, Bob Landry, Al Laney, Paul Henry Lang, Henry Langer, William Lynch, E. Lyman, W. J. Burke-Look, Frances Lyon, LARA-Elizabeth Reiss Alexander Lewis, Fred Luchs, Miss Lawson, Toshiko Ohsawa, LARA-Esther B. Rhoads.
    - 7. Folder. M - 2 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Lewis Mumford, A.J. Muste, George Murdock, Tracy D. Mygatt, Tom McNeil, J.P. Bethel-Merriam Co., Mrs. Frederic March, Pierre Burton-Maclean's Magazine, Mailings Inc., Edyth Milberg, Richmond Miller-The Messenger, Otto von Simson Measure, Linda Mangelsdorf, Brien McMahon (Senator), E.B. Moorehouse, Christopher Morley, Dorothy McFadden, Elsa Maxwell, Mollie Moon, Milton McLean, Micheal Mok, Hal McIntosh, Ashley Montagu, Henry Lee Moon, Walter Murphy, Lawrence Mayers, Carey McWilliams, Kenneth McCormick, Fern Maddox, Robert Mahoney, Theodore Malcolm, Martin Mane, Thomas Mann, Alan Olmstead-Manchester Evening Herald
  - Document Case # 82. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. M - 2-, 1949. (Box 320)
      Merle Miller, F. DeWolfe Miller, Edyth Milberg, Leo Miller, [UNK] Minuto, Bernard Mishkin, Douglas [UNK], Ashley Montagu, Dale Morgan, William Morris Agency, Walter Mosse, Charles Edgerton, Montclair Education Assoc., Ernest [UNK], Louise Thomas, Arthur Motley, Edgar Ansel Mowrer, H. J. Muller, Harold Mantell, Pieree Matisse, Grace Mayer, Lawrence Mayers, Herbert Mayes, Malcolm R. McBride, Mrs. McBride, John McCaffery, Margaret MacColl, Jinx McCrary, John McCutcheon, Dorothy McFadden, Archibald MacLeish, Senator Brien McMahon, [UNK] [UNK] McMurray, Virginia Patterson-the Macmillan Co., McMurray's the Personal Bookshop, Thomas Means, A.A. Medved, Measure A Critical Journal, Frederic Melcher, Cord Meyer,James A. Michener, Lamar Middleton, J.A. Migel
    - 2. Folder, N. (Box 320)
      Harry Carman-N.Y. Adult Education Council, Everett Clinchy-National Conference of Christians and Jews, Mildred Fenner-National Education Assoc. of the U.S., The New School for Social Research, Heinz Norden, James Nield, J.J.Singh-India League of America (Nehru), Jerome Nathanson, Maurice Rosenblatt-National Committee for an Effective Congress, James Lambie-National Committee for Free Europe, Elinore Herrick-National Citizen's Council on Civil Rights, Allen Nevins, Nathan Field, Richard Neuberger, Leo Nevas, Sigmund Neumann, Victor Waybright-The New American Library, Paul Hoffman, Geoffrey Hellman-The New Yorker, Frida Nielsen, John Swomley-National Council Against Conscription, A.J. Carlson-National Society for Medical Research, Stanley Noble, [UNK] Symphony Society.
    - 3. Folder. S - 1 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Gustave Simons, Robert Mercer, State [UNK] Commission, Dale Stafford, [UNK] Schilp, Wiliam Sadowsky, Merritt Stone Jr., San Francisco State College-Seminar in Europe, Milo Sutliff, Milton Smith, I. Snapper, Kathleen Sproul, Mort Singer, Alix Szilasi, Upton Sinclair, John Sullivan, Margaret Sebree, Arthur Schlesinger, Horace Sutton, Sidney Satenstein, Laurence Salisbury, Marquess of Salisbury, Robert [UNK] William Comb, Herbert Schneider, Guy Emery Shipler, Norman Smith, William Sloane, Bernard Sobel, Edward Schmerler, [UNK] Schary, H. Scherbak, M.B. Schnapperz, Georges Schreiber, Charlotte [UNK], Judge Samuel Seabury, Julius Seligson, [UNK] Shapley, Max Schuster, Clifford Shaw, Harris Shevelson, Roger Shaw, Judge Sherry.
    - 4. Folder. S - 2 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Guy Emery Shipler, Mary Shipley, James Shotwell, George Shuster, Lawrence Siegel, Henry Simon, Dick Schuster, Anabel Simpson, Gregg Sinclair, Spyros [UNK], Upton Sinclair, Herbert Sloan, William Sloane, Harry Slochower, [UNK] Smedley, Bernard [UNK], Bernard Smilowitz, Allen Smith, Paul Smith, Smith College-Prof. Esther C. Dunn, Norman Smith, Susan Smith, Leon Schinasi Assoc., Edgar Snow, Bernard Sobel, Norma Miller-Society for the Prevention of WW III, Bill Soskin, Sound Stages Inc., Judith Staples, Roy Stryker, Joe Barnes and Bartley Crum-New York Star, Mark Starr, Mrs. John Stewart, Alfred Steinberg, Abram Spanel, Norman Isaacs-St. Louis Star, Rex Stout, Nathan Straus, Roger Straus, Harold Strauss, Hope Stewart, Frank Sullivan, Gael Sullivan, Ellen Sulzberger, Aaron Sussman, Herbert [UNK] Swope, Arthur Schlesinger Jr., Kathleen [UNK], A.A. Suppan
    - 5. Folder. T. (Box 320)
      Norman Taylor, Tobe, Diana Trillings, Ordway Tead, Bernard Drew, Telford Taylor, Nelson Talbott Jr., Kiyoshi Tanimoto, Frank Erager, Nathaniel Maxwell-Thoughtways, Annexation Agreement Between the U.S. and Texas-The Texas State Teachers Assoc., Charles Tennyson, Lon Tinkle, Goodwin Watson-Teachers College, Malcolm Ross-20th Century-Fox Film Corp., Norman Thomas, Dr. Terhune, Sarah Augusta Taintos, Elbert Thomas, Nelson Talbott, Mary Toppi, Bud Talbott, Herbert Welte--Techears College of Conn., Monte Bartlett Thornton, Jerry Tallmer, W. W. Teece, Mrs. M.S. Turk, Catherine [UNK], Jay Tower, Robert Trout, James Thurber, Grover Theis, Harriet Tracy, Doris Lavelle, Corlisa Lamont, Norman Taylor, Catherine [UNK], Tracy Tyler, Mrs. Edward Thomas, Mrs. Bernard Tomson, Tom Townsend, Helen Tapper, Shepard Traube, Clara Tead, Ralph Pitcher, Ruth Teiser, Lovell Thompson, John Thompson, Henry Luce-Time, Alfred Baker-Time Magazine, Louise Brown, Arnold Toynbee, Marian Carter-The Town Hall, Frank Tubridy.
    - 6. Folder. P -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Charles Prince, Princeton Film Center, Wilferd Peterson, William Patterson, Laurence Sebel-Phi Sigma Delta's Ruby Celebration, Jane Hudson-P.E.N. Club, Jack Cominsky, Fred Smith, Book Service for Newspapers, K.B. Elliot, Red Motley-Parade, The "Point Four" Program by James Warburg, Rosemary Park, William Parker, Edwin MacEwan-Paterson Chamber of Commerce, Floyd and Betty Pattee, John Pearson, Houston Peterson, F.W. Perocter, Prof. Ralph Barton Perry, Anna Laise Phillips, Merlyn Pitzele, article from Plain Talk by Asher Brynes, Mrs. E.E. Piper, Laura Huxtable Porter, Post War World Council, Orville Prescott, K.S. [UNK], Inc., Clifford Snaw,Senator Brien MacMahon, Mrs. Henry Leach-Public Ed. Assoc.
  - Document Case #83. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. R - 1 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      Walter Orr Roberts, Frederick Rinehart, Lt. Cmdr. J.C. Reardon, Allen Rivkin, Sylvia Rodenbach, Ruth Rome, William Rosenblum, Beardsley [UNK], Cowl Rider, Philip Ewald-Rineharf, The Reader's Bigest-DeWitt Wallace, Charles [UNK] Reader's Digest, Bob Ross, Stanley Rugg, Janet Roe, G.D. Rudd, Arthur Hays Sulzaberger, George Reetz, Rossell Hope Robins, Elizabeht Clarke Reiss, Burton Raffel, Mary R. Rondeau, Frank Ramsey, Radcliffe College, Simon [UNK], Mrs. Kermit Roosevelt (Peter [UNK] Next Voter) Anna Roosevelt, Ira Reid, Louis Ruppel, N. Crwin Rush, Valentine Sorokin-Embassy of the USSR, Franz Rubinow, Leo Doyle, Louis Dolivet, James Rosenberg, Earl Ross, [UNK] Florance-Reader's Digest
    - 2. Folder. R - 2 -, 1949. (Box 320)
      D. Wallace-Reader's Digest, Beardsley Roml, Irwin Robinson, Robert Rosamond, Carlos Romulo, Cowl Rider, Ben Ray Redman, Helen Appleton Read, Burton [UNK], Roger W. Riis, Donald Klopfer, Maule-Random House, Byron Colling, Bayard Rustin, Francis Russell, John William Rogers, Alan Raphael, James Shotwell, Russell Rhodes, Rebecca and Dean Richardson, Bob Ran, Emery Reves, Quentin Reynolds, Norman Richardson, Ranald [UNK] and Co., Frederick Rine-hart, Stanley Rinehart, Stewart Robb, Frederick Robin, Henry Robinson, Nelson Rockefeller, Wellington, Roe, John Wm Rogers, Ruth Bryan Owen Rohde, Eleanor Roosevelt, Fred Rosen, Percy Knauth, Alison Raymond, Dean James Russell.
    - 3. Folder. Roosevelt - Spellman Controversy. (Box 320)
      Grenville Clarke, Rocherster, Robert Hutchins, Keith Funston, Helen Cunningham, [UNK] Reid, Wm Green, Frank Graham, C.A. [UNK], J.W. Harrelson, Myron Taylor, AR Robb, Arhtur Fox, Albert C Jacobs, Josephine Jasper, Samuel Callaway, List of Potential Signers
    - 4. Folder. Town Hall Trip. (Box 320)
      John Nelson, Memo, mailing address for members, Helen Wessells, application, background editorial info., Chester Williams, World Town Hall Seminar, Visa aplication, Freedom's [UNK] Rings Round the World (pamphlet)
    - 5. Folder. Town Meeting Mutual. Town Hall scripts, talks, clippings, Elizabeth Schenk, articles, talk on alcohol. (Box 320)
    - 6. Folder. Town Meeting. Am. Broadcasting Co., "Good Evening Neighbors!"-America's Town Meeting of the Air, George V. Denny Jr., C.R. Pettes. (Box 320)
    - 7. Folder. Town Hall Club. Sture Mathew, Mary Grimes, Thurston Davies, Charles Beckwith, Wm Traum, Elizabeth Colclough, Wilbur Nelson, Walter Cooking (Box 320)
    - 8. Folder. Thyssen. article, trial, Regarding: Thyssen Trial, Thyssen vs. Reves, photocopies, letter to Fritz Thyssen (Box 320)
    - 9. Folder. U. (Box 320)
      Esther Stamats-United Council of Church Women, Mrs. Richard Loengard-United Negro College Fund, Harold Bentley-University of Utah Press, Leah Trelease-Univ. of Illinois, Mrs. J.D. Williams-Univ. of Mississippi, Dean Spalding-Univ. of Ill., Clifton Utley, Avis Schulman-United Jewish Appeal, Jean Starr Untermeyer, W. T. Couch-Univ. of Chicago Press, Charles Werz, Fred Werner Neal, Charles Probes, John Ullman, Organizations Cooperating in All-Day Conference on the United [UNK] Nations, Datus Smith-Assoc. of Am. University Presses, Louis Untermeyer.
    - 10. Folder. V. (Box 320)
      The Viking Press, Gore Vidal, Dorothy Shereff, Fritz von Windegger, Henry Volk, Everett Fontaine, Amy Vanderbuilt, Mamie Volpe, Carl Van Doren, Ted Van Fossen, James Patteson III-Vitamin Productz Co., Harriet Van Horne, William Veale, Jerry Voorhis, Rafael Heliodore Valle, Eleanor Van Alen-Training Americans for World Careers, Carroll Van Court, John Vizzard, Ben Huebsch-Viking Press.
    - 11. Folder. Summer Welles. corres. (Box 320)
    - 12. Folder. Wharton. Paul Newlon, Evolution and the Erotic Impulse, Stock Ownership of Saturday Review Assoc.,J.R. Cominsky, Ada McCormick. (Box 320)
    - 13. Folder. XYZ. (Box 320)
      Clara Leiser-Youth of all Nations, Inc., Hideki Yukawa, Chester Kerr, Yale Univ. Press, Fred Zepp, Jack Zaiman, Mitsuo Yamagishi, Paul Yaig Mrs. Barton Yount, Robert Young, Robert Dresser-The Yale Literary Magazine, Blanche Yurka, Stanley Young, William Hitzig, Frederic Zeman, Samuel Zemurray, William Ziff,
  - Document Case #84. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. A. (Box 320)
      The American Academy of Political and Social Science, Mrs. Louis Azrael, Ella Alford, Russell Anderson, A.M. Pitcher-The Authors Guild, Richard Andrews, Raymond Allen, T. S. Repplier-The Advertising Council, Frank Altschul, Devere Allen, Frederick Alexander, Mariana Amram, MacEnnis Moore-American Council of Voluntary Agencies for Foreign Service, Allen White-American Friends Service Committee, Aerial Livery, Dean Paul Shipman Andrews, Dean Achesoh, Raymond Allen, Cyrilly Abels, Reverend Norman Anderson, Ahad Polier,Dorothy Aylward, Paul Andrews, Beatrice Auerbach, Abercrombie & Fitch, Edward Aswell, Shannon Allen, Sadie Alexander, Russell Anderson, Mrs. Curtis Amen, Pearl Kluger-American Committee for Cultural Freedom.
    - 2. Folder. B. (Box 320)
      Thomas Hart Benton, George Brett, Edward Barrett, Sarah Ball, Dean Burchard, Elizabeth Buchanan, Ben Lucien Burman, Stringfellow Barr, Herbert Brucker, George Bye, G. A. Borgese, Stephen Benedict, George Brett, Sam Bierman, Winifred Bartlett, Phyllis Battelle, Hon. Frances Bolton, Dr. H.G. Burks Jr., Marjorie Browne, Wm Bottiglia, Lawrence Blochman, Donna Begen Baer, Harvey Breit, Clark Barrett, Wm Benton, Windsor Booth, Thomas Bledsoe, Aupela Bruce, Richard Brickner, Pearl S. Buck, Mary Lou Baker, John Bracken, Chester Bowles, Joseph Blumenthal, Thurman Barnard, Joseph Brewer, Robert Rockmore Barron, Rice & Rockmore, James Best, Benjamin Goldstein, T. L. Barnard, Charles, Burwell, William Rose Benet, Robert Bogen, Mrs. L.W. Brown, George Burr, Morroe Berger, Curtis Benjamin, Joseph Prandt, David Burrell, Leonora Berry, Commencement Exercises of Briarcliff Junior College, Joseph Brooks, John Barkham, Arno Bellack, David Bailey, Grace Burt, M. Brammer, Struthers Burt, Richard Bertrandias, Alice Bullock, T. Francis Bennett, A. V. Bodine, Antoinette Buchanan, Roland Gelatt-[UNK] Books, Hugh Behymer, Theodore Brameld, Herbert Brucker, Ulric Bell, William Benton, Ruth Barash, Bert Barker, Marshall Best, Julien Bryan, Elizabeht Mann Borgese, George Britt.
    - 3. Folder. C. (Box 320)
      Charles Cherringell, Elihu Cooper, Don Cougdon, Stuart Chase, Mrs. Norman Cox, Houston Cole, Page Cross, Estelle Clapp, Beryl Cohon, Mrs. Harold Cole, Ridgely Cummings, Bess Cunningham, Arch Crawford, David Cohn, Andrew Crichton, Alexander Clark, Hadley Cantril, Caravan Travel Club, Wm J. Calvert Jr., Agnes Clark, Anne Chambers, Dana Cotton, Thomas Collens, Howard Gorham-Carver Found,, Jacques Chambrus, Anna Caples, Kenneth Carter, Ralph Colp, John Cowles, Clarence Faust-Connecticut Educational Survey, Walter Mallory-Council on Foreign Relations, Henry Chauncey, Louise Clark, Raymond Crowley, Angelo Cohn, Thomas Collens, James Caldwell, Ruth Corbet, O.C. Carmicheel, M, K. Cooke, Henry Cabot, Stuart Chase, The Commonweal, Robert Christopher, W.L. Clayton, Swasey Crocker, Hadley Cantril, Raymond Crist, Harold Case, C.W. Chase, Ralph Colp, Henry Steele Commager, Gardner Cowles, Rina Clas, Mr. and Mrs. Candreva, Hon. ASJ Carnahan, Gordon Cole, Ted Cott, Elizabeth [UNK], Harry Carmen, Mr. Cominsky, Mable Frances Conant, W. B. Cotton Jr., Randolph Compton, Wm Christopherson, Margaret Clark, Will Clayton, Cass Canfield, Lucy Cores, Ted Cott, Alicia Cogan, George Counts, Jay H. Clow, James Keller-The Christophers.
    - 4. Folder. D. (Box 320)
      Malcolm Diamond, Frank Dobie, LeRoy Dreher, Wm Downton, A.F. Davies, Elber Davis, Mary Gould Davis, Virginius Dabney, Hon. Joseph Darst. Paul Ditzel, R. S. Damon, James Chambers-The Daily Times Herald, Lawrence Martin-The Denver Post, Emmett Dedmon, John Dobbin, Leigh Danenberg, E. DeGolyer, Arthur DuBrow, Watson Davis, Leo Doyle, Louis Dailey, Kanji Dwarkadas, Anastasia Dragon, Thomas [UNK], Harold Danziger, Joseph Daniels, Liube Drndic, Josephine Duveneck, Michel Dumont.
    - 5. Folder. East West Conference. Charles Odegaard, American Council of Learned Societies, U.N. Educational Scientific and Cultural Org.-Department of Cultural Activities. (Box 320)
    - 6. Folder. ECA Book Council. Hilda Livingston, The New American Liorary of World Literature, Hon. Wm Foster, Victor Weybright, Hon. Paul Hoffman. (Box 320)
  - Document Case #85. Personal and Business Correspondence.
    - 1. Folder. Engagements, 1951. (Box 321)
      John Everett, Rosamond Haas, Rex Stout-Writers Board for World Government, Ann Newbold, Hotel Statler, Elizabeth Bloch, Marshall Woods Fund, Elizabeth Colclough, Marc Rieffel, Wm Traum, Max Routtehberg, Chinni Sundram, Taraknath Das, Robert Williams, Richard Shaman, Roger Mastrude, Dorothy Norman, Richard Griffith, Edward Bernays, Eleanor Kask, N.Y. Newspaper Women's Club, Beryl Cohon, Hulda Goetz, David Lurensky, Hilton Buley, Dr. Minoo Masani, Clark Kuebler, C.A. Robinson Jr., Mrs. Harley Perkins, Nordecia Johnson, Mary Constantine, Clarence Pickett, D. Guerneey, Sir B. N. Rau, Oscar Israel, Arthur DuBrow, Rabbi Morris Kertzer, Rabbi Roland Gittelsohn, Max Franzen, Henry Walck, J.S. Doughty, A.V. Bodine, Paul Brooks, Charles Wilson, Isabel Leighton, Elmira College Commencement, N.J. State Teachers College, The American Education Fellowship, Eugene Wilkins, Colgate University, Bostonia-Boston University Alumni Mag. Susie Smith, C.G. Sargent, Eugene Wilkins, Ed Wegener, C.M. Stanley, Mrs. Edward Collier, George Field, Theodore Brameld, Thurston Davies, Wilmer Shultz, Mary Syke, Lewis Eldred, Mr. & Mrs. Edward Norman, Pauline Fairbanks, Mrs. Edward Collier, Mr. & Mrs. Rajeshwar Dayal, Helen Brandon, Seville Kistler, Rudolf Newburger, Howard Vickery, George Wulp, Pauline Fairbanks.
    - 2. Folder. E. (Box 321)
      F.E. Engelman, Edgar Ansell Mowrer, Henry Cabot, Donna Dagen Baer, S.M. Levitas, Dorianne Guernsey, Robert Leeper, Hedvig Sweetland, Meryle Evans, Eastern Airlines, Wm Emerson, James Eighelberger, Mary Elizabeth Edes, Arthur Elliot, W.W. Livengood, Lona Eldredge, Dwight Eisenhower, Morris Ernst, Allan Elston, Muriel Eldridge, Violet Edwards, Lewis Eldred, John Thompson Everitt, Ralph Ellsworth, Roger Evans
    - 3. Folder. F. (Box 321)